If you need to reduce or increase the wrinkle in the area, you can use the
brush.
The size of the brush is the size of the brush used in the area, and since the center of the
brush has a gradient effect, the center part is the highest value, and it gradually spreads
out, so you can control the gradient area through the gradient value.
Click and drag the mouse to draw the curve area along the required area.
After opening the simulation, you can see that the brush is now in the correct position.
After the simulation, you can see that there are many irregular wrinkles in the corresponding
area.
If you use it in some areas in the middle of the board, it will also form irregular wrinkles.
Next, let's take a look at the use of the negative value.
Through the negative shrink rate, some wrinkles can be flattened because the grid is
shrunk.
But this does not mean that the wrinkles on a whole board can be modified in this way,
it is just a partially applicable method.
You can see that although the middle part has a shrink rate, due to the stretching of the
grid, the wrinkles on both sides have increased.
Therefore, it is not recommended to use it in a large area when using it.
In the process of dealing with some skirt-like wrinkles, it is recommended to use it in the
middle of the board.
Next, let's take a look at the use of the negative value.
There are some skirts in the middle that have been created to tighten the waist and
body.
You can use the negative value of the grid to flatten the edges.
But if the shrink rate is very high, it may cause the problem of just adding a little
grid and getting too tight.
So it is better to try the negative value method and improve thechenic.
Next, let's look at the normal size.